Sentence #,Word,POS,Tag
Sentence: 47960,Marie,NNP,B-PER
,Curie,NNP,I-PER
,was,VBD,O
,a,DT,O
,pioneering,JJ,O
,scientist,NN,O
,in,IN,O
,the,DT,O
,field,NN,O
,of,IN,O
,radioactivity,NN,O
,.,.,O
Sentence: 47961,Marie,NNP,B-PER
,Curie,NNP,I-PER
,was,VDB,O
,the,DT,O
,first,JJ,O
,woman,NN,O
,to,TO,O
,win,VBD,O
,a,DT,O
,Nobel,NNP,O
,Prize,NNP,O
,.,.,O
Sentence: 47962,Pierre,NNP,B-PER
,Curie,NNP,I-PER
,was,VBD,O
,instrumental,JJ,O
,in,IN,O
,discovering,VBG,O
,radioactivity,NN,O
,.,.,O
Sentence: 47963,Pierre,NNP,B-PER
,Curie,NNP,I-PER
,and,CC,O
,Marie,NNP,B-PER
,Curie,NNP,I-PER
,were,VBD,O
,partners,NNS,O
,in,IN,O
,both,DT,O
,life,NN,O
,and,CC,O
,science,NN,O
,.,.,O
Sentence: 47964,Marie,NNP,B-PER
,Curie,NNP,I-PER
,was,VBD,O
,born,VBN,O
,in,IN,O
,Warsaw,NNP,B-GPE
,",",",",O
,Poland,NNP,I-GPE
,.,.,O
Sentence: 47965,What,WP,O
,did,VBD,O
,Marie,NNP,B-PER
,Curie,NNP,I-PER
,discover,VB,O
,?,.,O
Sentence: 47965,Where,WRB,O
,was,VBD,O
,Marie,NNP,B-PER
,Curie,NNP,I-PER
,born,VBN,O
,?,.,O
Sentence: 47966,What,WP,O
,was,VBD,O
,Marie,NNP,B-PER
,Curie,NNP,I-PER
,s,VBZ,O
,marital,JJ,O
,status,NN,O
,?,.,O
Sentence: 47966,Where,WRB,O
,did,VBD,O
,Marie,NNP,B-PER
,Curie,NNP,I-PER
,receive,VB,O
,her,PRP$,O
,early,JJ,O
,education,NN,O
,?,.,O
Sentence: 47967,Marie,NNP,B-PER
,Curie,NNP,I-PER
,discovered,VBD,O
,radium,NN,O
,in,IN,O
,1898,CD,O
,.,.,O
Sentence: 47967,Marie,NNP,B-PER
,Curie,NNP,I-PER
,has,VBD,O
,two,CD,O
,daughters,NNS,O
,named,VBN,O
,Irène,NNP,B-PER
,and,CC,O
,Ève,NNP,B-PER
,.,.,O
